Guide to the Spyros P. Skouras Papers M0509
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 9: Speeches
  - Various 1970
    - Order Of Lafayette Dinner Honoring SPS, 1970 Dec 7 (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Various 1971
    - "Aotos" Award Luncheon Honoring SPS, 1971 April 27 (Box 86, Folder 39)
    - Variety Clubs Convention, 1971 April 28 (Box 86, Folder 40)
    - Religious Heritage Of America SPS Award, 1971 June (Box 86, Folder 41)
  - Various - Undated
    - Actor Youth Fund Honoring Harold Gibbons (Box 86, Folder 42)
    - American Israel Cultural Foundation Dinner (Box 86, Folder 43)
    - American Men's Luncheon Club, Johannesburg, South Africa (Box 86, Folder 44)
    - American Mothers Committee (Box 86, Folder 45)
    - American Overseas Aid (Box 86, Folder 46)
    - "Children Of Palestine". (Box 86, Folder 47)
    - The Concentrated Essence Of Strategy (Box 86, Folder 48)
    - European Trip (Box 86, Folder 49)
    - Heart Award Dinner Speech (Box 86, Folder 50)
    - Hellenic. American Chamber Of Commerce (Box 86, Folder 51)
    - Introducing H.E. Panagiotis Canellopoulos (Box 86, Folder 52)
    - "Is Our Free Enterprise System Threatened By European Socialism" (Box 86, Folder 53)
    - Luncheon Honoring Hon. George Christopher, Mayor Of San Francisco (Box 86, Folder 54)
    - Motion Picture & Amusement Division Of The Jewish Appeal Luncheon (Box 86, Folder 55)
    - Notes To Be Incorporated In Speech To Be Made By SPS At Harvard (Box 86, Folder 56)
    - Red Cross (Box 86, Folder 57)
    - Shipping Speech Made By SPS (Box 86, Folder 58)
    - Si Fabian Dinner (Box 86, Folder 59)
    - Speech Delivered By SPS In Answer To Speech By Rector Of Natl. Autonomous Univ. Of Mexico (Box 86, Folder 60)
    - Suggestions For Ahepa Speech To The Hon. James P. Mitchell, Secretary Of Labor (Box 86, Folder 61)
    - UGOC (Box 86, Folder 62)
    - Variety Clubs (Box 86, Folder 63)
    - Welcome Dinner To Mr. Luce (Box 86, Folder 64)
    - The World Response To World Brotherhood, Brussels (Box 86, Folder 65)
    - World's Fair Greek Pavilion (Box 86, Folder 66)